My Lord.
How did they know our whereabouts?
Either they were following us all along,
or
someone in the Criminal Justice Department
tipped them off.
Check who entered or left under unusual circumstances
from last night to this morning.
I will go see Director Zhou.
Father once said
Zhou Yan is an old friend.
But seven years have passed,
and people's hearts change easily.
Director.
I examined a bizarre case last night.
I found this in the crevice of the coffin.
Please take a look.
This is official cloud-patterned brocade,
exclusively for officials above the sixth rank to make everyday clothes.
The worn part has
a special soap locust smell.
It is unique to the soap locust used by the laundry room
inside the Criminal Justice Department.
Are you saying
the killer might be
someone inside the Criminal Justice Department?
Or at least,
someone who can easily access officials' clothes in the department,
and carry them in and out
without attracting attention.
I will secretly
investigate this matter.
Archivist Shen,
this case involves a lot.
Let's put it aside for now.
I will assign someone else to it.
My Lord.
I have another doubt.
Seven years ago, why was the case file of the missing Prefect Gu Wenyuan of Yunzhou
a blank blood letter?
A blank blood letter?
Old cases
have long been sealed.
That file
might have become damp and mildewed.
Will damp and mildew
reveal seven bloody fingerprints and a prophecy?
Mo.
I have been friends with your father for many years.
Listen to me.
Some cases cannot be investigated.
For your sake,
and for
your father's reputation.
I have my own plans for this case.
Archivist Shen,
you have been overworked recently.
Rest for now.
You are not allowed to investigate further without orders.
Yes.
Uncle Zhou is warning me.
My Lord.
I found it.
From last night to this morning,
only Director's personal servant,
Zhou Fu,
went out late at night.
He said he was getting medicine for the Director,
but the direction he went
was not the pharmacy.
Abandoned Garden in the western suburbs.
There is indeed something suspicious.
Prepare a horse.
Let's go to the Abandoned Garden in the western suburbs.
Also,
send someone to secretly
keep an eye on Zhou Fu's family.
Yes, My Lord.
Mo'er,
you shouldn't have come.
Uncle Zhou,
what's in this well?
It was me.
I did it all.
I perverted the law,
conspired with thieves,
stole corpses from the mortuary,
and faked supernatural events.
I plead guilty.
Just arrest me.
Uncle Zhou.
Stealing corpses requires physical labor.
How could you do it
when you are old and weak?
This brother, Zhou Fu,
went out to get medicine this morning,
yet the soles of his shoes are stained
with the same red soil as here.
The person he went to see
was probably not a doctor.
Have mercy, My Lord.
Someone kidnapped
Director's young son,
forcing him to take the blame,
and forcing me to lead the way
to destroy things by this well.
I...
I was also forced.
It's over.
It's all over.
Hand over the Blood Chalcedony.
Director Zhou,
you failed in your duty,
and the master is very disappointed.
Since Registrar Shen insists on seeking death,
I'll grant your wish
and bury you in this well.
You led the way here to destroy things.
Destroy what?
They were thrown into the well.
Then let's go down and see.
My Lord.
Seal the well
and pour kerosene.
Man-made.
Not very old.
What did you throw down?
An oilcloth bundle.
They said it must sink to the bottom of the well,
the deepest part of the pool.
My Lord.
Tied to a stone at the bottom of the well.
Secret underground passage.
Array core.
Is this token a keepsake or a key?
Miss.
Escape the Nine Turns.
Mural
map.
This map
marks the underground secret room,
the passage,
and this mark.
The core position of
the Nine Turns Reincarnation Array.
My Lord,
the destiny charm in her hand.
Jiazi,
Yichou,
Bingyin.
This is my birth time.
Why is it carved on her destiny charm?
Is this birth character
a coincidence,
or...
This dry well has a special terrain.
It's perfect for trapping them.
Seal the well.
Secretly send someone to keep watch.